zoompf.com 2019-01-05

# Privacy Policy - Rigor

Updated: April 26, 2018

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our website visitors; this policy sets out how we will treat your personal information.

 **(1) What information do we collect?**

We may collect, store and use the following kinds of personal data:

(a) information about your visits to and use of this website and the websites of our clients;

(b) information about any transactions carried out between you and us on or in relation to this website, including information relating to any purchases you make of our goods or services;

(c) information that you provide to us for the purpose of requesting information, registering with us and/or subscribing to our website services and/or email notifications.

Our website is not directed to children under thirteen (13) years or age and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13.

 **(2) Information about website visits**

We may collect information about your computer and your visits to this website such as your IP address, geographical location, browser type, referral source, length of visit and number of page views. We may use this information in the administration of this website, to improve the website’s usability, and for marketing purposes.

We use cookies on this website. A cookie is a text file sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The text file is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.

We may send a cookie which may be stored on by your browser on your computer’s hard drive. We may use the information we obtain from the cookie in the administration of this website, to improve the website’s usability and for marketing purposes. We may also use that information to recognize your computer when you visit our website, and to personalize our website for you. Our advertisers may also send you cookies.

Most browsers allow you to refuse to accept cookies. (For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector.) This will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one.

 **(3) Using your personal data**

Personal data submitted on this website will be used for the purposes specified in this privacy policy or in relevant parts of the website.

In addition to the uses identified elsewhere in this privacy policy, we may use your personal information to:

(a) improve your browsing experience by personalizing the website;

(b) respond to your comments, requests or inquiries;

(c) send information (other than marketing communications) to you which we think may be of interest to you by post or by email or similar technology;

(d) send to you marketing communications relating to our business or the businesses of carefully-selected third parties which we think may be of interest to you by post or, where you have specifically agreed to this, by email or similar technology.

(e) provide other companies with statistical information about our users.

We do not receive or store credit card information from registered users. We use an outside credit card processing company to bill you for services. The unaffiliated credit card processing company does not retain, share, store or use your personally identifiable information for any other purposes, however, we cannot guarantee that there won’t be a security breach of the outside credit card processing company.

We may obtain your written consent from time to time in electronic form by using online agreements or other acknowledgements through our application, including for any other contemplated uses of your personal data not addressed in this privacy policy. Please read all online agreements carefully before accepting them.

We use the contact information provided by an entity to communicate with individuals working on behalf of such entity.  Therefore, you may receive a communication from us in response to a request by your employer or the manager of an account to add you as a registered user.  

 **(4) Products and Clients**

Rigor is the maker of the Rigor application, an application testing and monitoring suite. Rigor sells and distributes the Rigor application to third party clients who may use it to test and monitor their own applications, including those applications hosted and managed by third parties. While Rigor sells only to ethical clients, it cannot be held responsible if its clients engage in unethical use of the information gathered by or functionality contained within the Rigor application.

 **(5) Other disclosures**

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere in this privacy policy, we may disclose information about you (within or outside your country of residence):

(a) to the extent that we are required to do so by law;

(b) in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings;

(c) in order to establish, exercise or defend our legal rights (including providing information to others for the purposes of fraud prevention and reducing credit risk);

(d) with third parties who provide services to us in the provision of the Services to our clients, including our technology providers, payment card processor, administrative personnel and providers and professional advisors; 

(e) in connection with a merger or reorganization; and

(f) when we are acting as a data processor at the direction of our client (data controller), at the request of the client. 

Please review Rigor’s security policy at [http://rigor.com/trust](http://rigor.com/trust) for detailed information about the third party service providers to Rigor who process data on our behalf. 

**(6) Security and storage of your personal data**

We will take reasonable precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information. Of course, data transmission over the Internet is inherently insecure, and we cannot guarantee the security of data sent over the Internet.

We will store all the personal information you provide on our secure servers. Rigor may also store Your login or password information for any third party applications You denote as a connector. These may include, but are not limited to, Google Analytics. This information is encrypted for security and is used solely to provide a connection between the Rigor application and the third party application and will not be shared with any entity other than the third party in question.

You are responsible for keeping your passwords confidential. We will not ask you for your passwords.

Please review Rigor’s security policy at [http://rigor.com/trust](http://rigor.com/trust) for detailed information about our data security practices and list of sub-processors.

We retain the personal information we collect for so long as reasonably necessary to fulfill the purposes for which the data was collected, to perform our contractual and legal obligations, and for any applicable statute of limitations periods for the purposes of bringing and defending claims.

 **(7) Legal basis for processing**

We rely on the following legal grounds to process your personal information:

Consent. We may use your personal information as described in this privacy policy subject to your consent.  To withdraw your consent, please contact us at info@rigor.com. You may also refrain from providing, or withdraw, your consent for cookies. Please see   
“Your rights and choices” section below for more information on opt-outs.

Performance of a contract. We may need to collect and use your personal information and the personal information of your customers, as applicable, to perform our contractual obligations. When we process personal information on behalf of third parties, we do so pursuant to agreements with such third parties.

Legitimate Interests. We may use your personal information for our legitimate interests to provide our services and to improve our services and the content on our application.  We process information on behalf of third parties who have legitimate interests in operating their businesses. We may use technical information as described in this privacy policy and use personal information for our marketing purposes consistent with our legitimate interests and any choices that we offer or consents that may be required under applicable law.  

 **(8) Your rights and choices**

We communicate with our registered members on a regular basis via email. For example, we may use your email address to confirm your request, to send you notice of payments, to send you information about changes to our products and services, and to send notices and other disclosures as required by law. Users can opt-out of all email communications from Rigor by contacting us at info@rigor.com. We will process your unsubscribe request as soon as possible, but please be aware that in some circumstances you may receive a few more messages until your request is processed. You also may opt-out of receiving such emails by clicking on the “unsubscribe” link within the text of the applicable email.

You may contact us to request information about the personal data we have collected from you and to request the correction, modification or deletion of such personal information, which requests we will do our best to honor subject to any legal and contractual obligations.  To make a request or to ask us a question about our data practices, please contact us via email at info@rigor.com. 

In addition, you may contact us at the address set forth at the end of this policy.

Subject to local law, you may have additional rights under the laws of your jurisdiction regarding your personal data, such as the right to complain to your local data protection authority. 

You may also refrain from providing, or withdraw, your consent for cookies. You may be able to disable cookies through your browser settings, but if you delete or disable cookies, you may experience interruptions or limited functionality in certain areas of the website.

We use Google Analytics, a web analytics service of Google Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses cookies to identify the frequency of use of certain areas of our website and to identify preferences. The information regarding your use of this website that is generated by the cookie (including your truncated IP address) is transferred to a Google server in the United States and stored there. Google will use this information to analyze your use of the website, compile reports on website activity for us, and perform further services associated with website use and Internet use. Google may also transmit this information to third parties where required by law or to the extent that third parties process these data on behalf of Google.

You can deactivate Google Analytics using a browser add-on if you do not wish the website analysis to take place. You can download the add-on here:  [www.tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptou](http://www.tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptou)t.

 **(9) Policy amendments**

We may update this privacy policy from time-to-time by posting a new version on our website. You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are happy with any changes.

 **(10) Third party websites**

The website contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy policies of third party websites.

 **(11) California disclosures**

California Information-Sharing Disclosure: California residents may request a list of all third parties with respect to which we have disclosed any information about you for direct marketing purposes and the categories of information disclosed.  If you are a California resident and want such a list, please send us a written request by email to info@rigor.com with “California Privacy Rights” in the subject line. 

California Do Not Track Disclosure: We use commercially reasonable efforts to respond to a user’s Do Not Track browser settings through the use of a third party plug-in utilized on Rigor.com.  The plug-in is developed and maintained by a third party, and Rigor makes no representations and warranties as to its performance and effectiveness. 

**(12) Jurisdiction and Contact Information**

Rigor is a Georgia limited liability company.  Our websites are controlled and operated from the United States. If you are an individual from the European Economic Area, the United Kingdom, Canada or any other jurisdiction with laws or regulations governing personal data collection, use, and disclosure that differ from United States laws, please be advised that we may store the information we collect in the United States or in other countries where we or our third-party service providers have operations.  Personal data may also be transferred from the country of your residence to other countries, including the United States.

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or our treatment of your personal data, please write to us by email to info (at) Rigor.com or by post to Rigor, Inc., 3423 Piedmont Rd NE, Atlanta, GA 30305.
